Taking the example from the previous video,
接着上个视频的示例
let's say you wanted to extract
假如你想要从同一列文本数据中
two different kinds of features from the same text column,
提取两种特征
"tfidf" values and the length of the text.
"tf-idf" 值和文本的长度
You're first approach might be to create an additional column from the text column,
你的第一种方法可以是根据文本数据列新建一列
called 'text_length', like this.
叫做 'text_length' 像是这样
Then, both text and text_length can be part of your future matrix.
然后 文本列 text 和 text_length 列都会出现在后续的矩阵中
But now your pipeline would break.
但是会导致你的管道不能正常工作
You can't run CountVectorizer on NumPy arrays of strings and numbers.
你不能在字符串和数据组成的 NumPy 数组上运行 CountVectorizer
Now, let's say you had a custom transformer called TextLengthExtractor.
现在 假设我们有一个自定义的转换器 TextLengthExtractor.
Now, you could leave x_train as
这样的话 你可以保留 x_train
just original text column if you could figure
作为原始的文本数据列
out how to add the TextLengthExtractor to your pipeline,
只要你能找到办法将 TextLengthExtractor 加入到你的管道里即可
if only you could fit your TextLengthExtractor on the original text data,
只需使用 TextLengthExtractor 拟合原始的文本数据
rather than the output of the previous transformer.
而不是拟合前一个转换器的输出数据
But you need both the outputs of the TfidfTransformer
但是同时需要 TfidfTransformer 的输出
and the TextLengthExtractor to feed into the classifier as input.
和TextLengthExtractor 的输出作为分类器的输入
FeatureUnions are super helpful for handling these situations,
FeatureUnions 在应对这种需要时非常方便
where we need to run two steps in parallel,
即在同一份数据上
on the same data,
并行运行两个步骤
and combine the results to pass into the next step.
并且将结果综合起来送入下一步的情况
Like pipelines, FeatureUnions are built using a list of key value pairs,
和管道一样 FeatureUnions 通过键值对的列表创建
where the key is a string for what you want to name
其中 键是字符串 是步骤的名称
a step and the value is the estimator object.
值是评估器对象
Also, similarly, a FeatureUnion combines
类似地 FeatureUnion 将
a list of estimators to become a single estimator.
一列评估器组合成一个评估器
However, it runs its estimators in parallel,
不同的是 它的评估器是并行运行的
rather than in sequence, like pipelines.
而不是像管道一样串行执行
In this example, the estimators being run in parallel are nlp_pipeline and text_length.
在这个例子中 并行运行的两个评估器是 nlp_pipeline 和 text_length
Notice that we use a pipeline in the FeatureUnion to make sure
注意我们 FeatureUnion 中使用了管道以确保
the CountVectorizer and the TfidfTransformer steps are still running in sequence.
CountVectorizer 和 TfidfTransformer 两个步骤是串行执行的
Now, our pipeline doesn't break and uses both features.
现在 我们的管道正常运行并且使用了两个特征
This would actually be equivalent to this code.
这和这份代码的效果是一样的
After initializing all the estimators,
初始化所有的评估器后
notice that the CountVectorizer and
注意到 CountVectorizer 和
the TextLengthExtractor are both feed and transformed onto the original training data.
TextLengthExtractor 的输入和转换都使用了原始的训练数据
Then, their outputs are combined and passed in to the classifier.
然后 它们的输出结合起来被传入分类器
Similarly, with the test data,
类似地 在测试数据上
the CountVectorizer and TextLengthExtractor,
CountVectorizer 和 TextLengthExtractor
both transform the original test data,
都对原始的测试数据做了转换
and the results are combined to pass into the classifier.
然后其结果被结合起来传入分类器